我看到你的书了
I found your book.
我肯定作品一旦发表  作者就会现身
I'm sure once it's published, the author will come forward.
总会有一个人喜欢
There's a certain someone that might actually like
丹和我心灵相通
Dan and I have a real connection.
我需要先确定你的感觉和我一样
I need to know for certain that you feel as I do.
你愿意嫁给我吗？
Will you marry me?
你是查莉表妹吧？
You are cousin Charlie?
我不得不说这是个非常精明的计划
I have to say it was a pretty devious plan.
谢谢你  艾薇  你表现得很好
Thank you, Ivy. You played your part perfectly.
我们拥有的是伟大的爱
What we have is a great love.
我要去和路易说分手了
I should find Louis and tell him it's over.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
这是你获得幸福的好机会
This is your chance at happiness.
你值得拥有自己的童话
You deserve your fairy tale.
但我必须放手让你走
But I need to let you go.
现在这不是你的任务了
So this is not your assignment now.
转下地球仪  选个地方
Just spin the globe and pick a point.
天哪  这光线衬得你像天鹅一样美
God, you're such a swan in this light.
那时候的人就是这幅德行
That's how these people were back then.
谢谢
Thanks.
马歇尔  你不是说过
Marshall, remember when you said
谢谢
Thank you.
我以为你还在伦敦
I thought you'd still be in London,
所以我就提前来这里
So I came back here early,
很高兴你能来
happy to have you.
不知道她有没有邀请恰克
Wonder if she invited Chuck.
挺好的  你不在
Great. You were gone.
那证明我在做很正点的事
it means I'm doing something right.
回家的感觉如何？
How does it feel to be home?
但也许我们应该把婚礼计划丢到一边
But maybe we should skip the wedding planning
我们不能再让父母等下去了
we can't put off our parents any longer.
艾伯特的演讲比安眠药还能催眠
Albert's speeches are stronger than Ambien.
我是觉得自己好幸运
I do consider myself lucky.
我是你坚强的后盾
I'm your rock.
一切有我在呢
You can count on me.
你们怎么来了这里？
How did you guys end up here?
你自己问他吧
Ask him yourself.
瑟琳娜
Serena.
我知道你们会说什么
I know what you're gonna say.
丹尼尔
Daniel.
我昨天还想起来你了呢  老伙计
I was thinking about you just yesterday, old boy.
故事讲的什么内容？
What's the story about?
我迫不及待想看你穿上它的样子
I can't wait to see you in it.
不用了  谢谢
No, thank you.
我觉得我该把我的精力放在下一轮上
I think I need all my wits for the next round.
我这个夏天一开始就戒酒了
I gave up drinking at the beginning of summer.
继续吧  你们俩该喝一杯
Come on. You guys need one.
干杯
Cheers.
至少这个秘密马上就要不攻自现了
At least this secret is bound to show itself soon.
他对索菲唯命是从
He conceded to Sophie on everything.
我敢肯定他在尽可能地维持和平关系
I'm sure he's just trying to keep the peace the best he can.
我还没说到最糟糕的地方呢
I haven't even told you the worst part yet.
他们想让我穿索菲的婚纱
They want me to wear Sophie's dress.
无论你穿什么都会很漂亮的
you're gonna look beautiful in whatever you wear,
你那边还没忙完吗？
Aren't you done out there?
瑟琳娜  你的客人刚刚进来
Serena, your guests just came through the gate.
好的 谢谢  我马上过去
Okay, thank you. I'll be right there.
再见
Bye.
我知道她们在吃午饭
I know they're on lunch.
没问题
Sure.
我不记得有允许你的朋友来探班
I don't remember approving a set visit for your friends.
你一定就是马歇尔
You must be Marshall.
您是哪位？
And who are you?
我可以带你去看看
I could show you.
你们知道我会说什么
You know what I have to say.
那就去吧
Then go.
去工作吧
Get back to work.
现在他走了  去找简吧
But now he's gone. Go find Jane.
你会做得很棒的
You're gonna be great.
是的  我扛得住
Yeah, I'll totally hold.
谢谢  埃普莉
Thanks, Epperly.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
你要去哪？
Where you going?
你没跟你妈妈说
You didn't talk to your mother.
我真的很难拒绝她的要求
It's just so hard to say no to her.
我只是在缓和她对于我们未来的威胁
I'm trying to ease her into our future.
未来就是现在了
The future is here.
我们再过三个月就结婚了
We're gonna be married in three months.
我必须得确定我们站在同一条战线上
I need to know that we're in this together,
准备做什么？
Ready for what?
瑟琳娜  你来找马歇尔吗？
Serena. Are you looking for Marshall?
我不是想给别人添麻烦
I'm not trying to get anyone in trouble.
你今晚有空吗？
You free tonight?
我也是
Me, too.
在好莱坞的每个人都重新做人了
Everyone in Hollywood reinvents themselves.
你一定会很不开心的
you are not gonna be happy.
你之前是在汉普顿吗？
You were in the Hamptons?
从这开始你得小心点
You gotta take it easy up here.
我一点都不怕
I'm not scared.
我什么都不怕
I'm not scared of anything.
你怎么能这样对我？
How could you do this to me?
你以为我不知道  你打的是什么主意吗？
You think I didn't know what you were up to?
怎么了？
What's going on?
有人耍了我
Someone played a joke on me,
对不起
I'm sorry.
我们想好要干嘛
We decided what we wanted,
你毫不犹豫地承担了责任
You accepted responsibility without hesitation
我们已经长大了
We're growing up.
不管怎么说  对不起
Anyway, I'm sorry,
但是跟你在一起很开心
but I still had a lot of fun with you.
我也是  我接受你的道歉
As did I. And I accept.
说不定我们还能再见面呢
Maybe we'll see each other around sometime.
没错
Yeah.
再见
Good-bye.
回见
Bye.
你想见我吗？
You wanted to see me?
我需要像你这样甘于奉献  充满热情的人
I need someone with your dedication and fire.
好
Yeah.
我非常乐意
I would love to.
莉莉又和设计师开会去了
Lily has another meeting with the decorator.
她已经重装修好几次了  但感觉都一个样
She's redecorated so many times, it looks exactly the same.
喔  对了  你写的故事很棒
Oh, and by the way, your story was amazing.
简给了我一份工作
Jane offered me a job.
谢谢
thank you.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你真美
you look beautiful.
他们知道了吗?
Do they know?
知道什么?
Know what?
他们给过我你的尺寸
They sent me your measurements.
因为我没怀孕
Because I'm not pregnant.
随你怎么说
Lie to me all you want,
真是难以置信
It's crazy.
不会  我很高兴能离开那里
No, I'm just glad to be away from there.
艾薇  别跟你男友闲聊了  赶紧开工
Ivy, stop talking to your boyfriend and start working.
你迟到了
You're late.
你在这里干什么呢?
What are you doing here?
真奇怪
That was weird.
我们还是出去吧
let's get out of here.
不论你愿意与否
Whether you want to or not.
见到你真好
So good to see you.